[OVERDO]
[Episode 21]
Say
you want me to leave with you,
and we will leave right now.
Shall we?
♪ The more passionate ♪
♪ Our past embrace ♪
♪ The more icy ♪
♪ Our present clash ♪
Let's go.
♪ If not tangled in love ♪
♪ We are locked in hate ♪
♪ There is no escaping it ♪
♪ Sharper pain, deeper mark ♪
♪ Deeper care, greater torment ♪
Don't be crazy.
♪ I won't give up on you ♪
♪ Don't let go of me ♪
♪ Let the ropes of fate ♪
♪ Bind you and me ♪
♪ Even if led to a precipice ♪
♪ Together, we fall ♪
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
♪ Love and hate till the very end ♪
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
♪ Never back down, hold my ground ♪
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Must be together ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
Wait.
I just want to say a proper goodbye.
After all, I'm going to die,
aren't I?
If you die,
he will live on
more easily with hatred,
won't he?
[Invitation]
Principal,
congratulations.
I'm sorry.
Why are you saying sorry to me?
It's just that
I'm afraid
I won't be able to attend your wedding.
I got an opportunity
to study at a foreign aviation school,
and I'll be leaving in a couple of days.
Why didn't you tell me about this?
It happened suddenly.
I'm sorry.
If there's nothing else,
I shall take my leave.
[Invitation]
Principal,
your wedding with Miss Fang
is just for show.
You
could have told Ms. Ye.
Different flight paths
lead to different destinations.
Only if I stay here
can she fly high and far.
[Three years ago]
Qingyu, stop drinking.
As the older brother,
I'm so useless.
To save my brother's life,
I could only watch
him go to prison with my own eyes.
Qingyu.
Forgive yourself.
Responsibility is sometimes a shackle.
It traps you
and keeps you from doing what you want.
Zhihong,
the burden I carry...
is just too much.
Qingyu.
[Zhenhua No. 1 Aviation School]
Why?
I've thought it through.
There is no future for us.
You are the eldest young master
of the Murong family,
the famous young marshal
of the Cheng Army,
while I'm just a helpless orphan.
But I don't care about that.
Don't misunderstand.
I don't mean to belittle myself.
What I care about
isn't the difference in status,
but the difference in responsibilities.
You willingly shoulder
too many responsibilities.
Your wife
has to be someone
who can share
your family's responsibilities.
But that's not what I want.
I don't want to lose my name
and my career...
confined for life
under the title of Mrs. Murong.
Principal.
In the future,
I will still be
your most outstanding pilot.
Why do you think
you'd lose your dreams by being with me?
Why...
won't you even give it a try?
Little airplane, come down! Come down!
Little kid.
What are you doing?
My airplane landed up there.
Miss, can you help me get it?
This wall is too high.
It's dangerous.
How do you know if you don't try?
So,
all good things are fleeting.
Qingyu.
You and I are on different paths—
we must eventually part ways.
Before I leave,
I can only do one last thing for you.
You're here.
If you hadn't come,
I might have really left.
Ms. Ye,
did you ask to meet me
because there's an emergency?
I know your plan.
I can help you.
This time,
I want to give it a try.
Be careful.
Hang it straight.
Young Master Boze, why are you here?
Mrs. Wang.
Tomorrow is the wedding.
I came to see
if there's anything I can help with.
You are so thoughtful, Young Master Boze.
These are just chores for the servants.
How could we trouble you?
That won't do.
Tomorrow is my brother's wedding.
As his younger brother,
I should naturally pay more attention.
Qingyi!
Why are you here?
I heard from Qingyu
that you were going abroad.
Goodness.
You have the nerve to come back?
Aren't you afraid of getting beaten?
I'm here to deliver a wedding gift.
What are you laughing at?
Seeing all these decorations today,
I thought it would be festive.
But why does this meal
feel like a meal at a funeral?
You just got beaten.
I see you never learn your lesson, right?
It's a joyous day—
would it kill you not to talk nonsense?
If you can only say good things
and not bad things,
then not many things
can be said in this family.
Didn't you say this wasn't your home?
Are you here to make everyone miserable?
Am I the one making people miserable?
Weren't things already miserable?
Everyone is putting on an act.
You did the deeds yourselves.
You chose this path yourselves.
Yet you feel miserable inside,
and still try to keep up appearances.
Does it feel good?
Young Master Qingyi,
that's enough.
Sister-in-law is truly
a respectable person.
It's just a pity that
the person Qingyu has in his heart
has never been you.
Qingyi,
show some respect.
Who do you want me to respect?
Who deserves my respect?
Qingyi.
If you have something to say,
we can talk about it after the meal.
What exactly is your purpose
for coming today?
Do you have to make everyone unhappy
in front of Boze
to be satisfied?
I've already said
I came today
to bring gifts to everyone.
Come in.
Give Madam Murong her gift first.
Seeing that your eyesight
is failing recently,
I specially got you a pair of glasses.
No need.
I can see clearly.
Can you really?
Then can you see clearly
who Qingyu
truly likes?
Can you see clearly
what exactly is mixed in
this marriage?
What are you saying?
Mother, you don't need to worry.
Men—
even if they fool around outside,
they will always come home.
Qingyu.
Is what he said true?
Do you have someone else
outside?
Qingyu.
I've told you many times
since you were a child
that you are the future
of the Murong family.
Your every move
and action
represents the Murong family.
If you have any
lowly women outside
who make fools of themselves,
when someone finds out about it,
embarrassment aside,
it would taint the Murong family's name.
Mother, watch your words.
Don't worry.
I know who I am
and what I should do.
Qingyu,
this is for you.
You will definitely like it.
What's this?
Ms. Ye wants to study abroad, right?
I got someone to get her a spot.
Since you like the UK so much,
you must let the person you love go there.
Don't you think so?
So it's you who applied for her.
I thank you on Ms. Ye's behalf.
Both of you are a perfect match.
You both are so broad-minded.
I guess—
where the sky is high,
the bird can fly anywhere.
Even if this bird
flies out of its own world,
you have to give it your blessings
in tears.
Isn't that right, Sister-in-law?
This is for you, Sister-in-law.
If one day you have a fight with Qingyu,
you can go to this place to cry.
If you don't like it,
you can just burn it.
[Land and Property Ownership Certificate]
[Buyer/Seller] [Currently residing at:]
[Ren Susu]
[Single-family home
at Shangbei, Xiangshuijian]
Thank you, Second Brother-in-law.
Is this a land deed?
Don't worry, sister.
I have something for you too.
I heard you wanted to learn how to shoot.
Today, your younger brother
will teach you how to shoot.
Watch closely.
♪ Hate is the smoke left by dying flames ♪
♪ Love is the warmth
lingering after the wildfire ♪
What are you doing?
♪ Love and hate collide in a blaze ♪
Qingyi.
♪ In this instant,
the flames rage out of control ♪
♪ Ahead lies
a tangle of joys and sorrows ♪
This family portrait—
with me, it's too crowded,
but without me, it's just right.
♪ Behind remains
the bitterness of unspoken feelings ♪
Doesn't it
♪ The heart races with every thought ♪
look more pleasing to the eye now?
♪ Yet remains forever bound ♪
I'll skip this meal.
♪ This spark of wildfire
spreading across the plains ♪
I wish you both
♪ Stirs embers that refuse to fade ♪
a long and loving life together
in advance.
♪ I seize fate by the hand ♪
♪ Accusing it of refusing to relent ♪
♪ Even in the scorching fire ♪
♪ I still hold onto
my unwavering obsession ♪
♪ As long as I can get this love ♪
♪ It doesn't matter
if it's fortune or misfortune ♪
Boze,
eat.
A long life...
Is the Huo family
gone just like this?
Huo Minxian.
Who's there?
A generation of the Huo family,
blown away by the wind and rain.
Miss Huo, are you really willing
to accept this?
Whether I do or not,
what does it have to do with you?
Fang Mulan and the Murong family
are investigating things
they shouldn't know.
And the Huo family's current situation
is also related to them.
So we are on the same boat.
You want to use me.
I don't care that those two bastards
from the Huo family are dead.
The Huo grandfather and grandson
treated you harshly,
so naturally
you have no attachment to them.
But what about your father
who died tragically in Beicheng,
Huo Mingxi?
What do you mean?
This woman
is not some Young Miss of the Fang family.
Her story
is closely related to your hatred.
[Marriage Notice:
Murong Qingyu & Fang Mulan]
Let me
tell you about it in detail.
[The Great World]
Sir,
are you alone?
Do you want me to keep you company?
By drinking with me?
Of course.
Scram.
What are you doing?
Drink less.
Drinking is bad for your health.
Why torture yourself like that
for Miss Fang?
How do you know?
I asked Jinrui.
I asked her
why you went crazy today.
She told me what happened a few days ago.
Indeed.
Miss Fang is gentle and intelligent—
truly captivating.
But Qingyi,
Miss Fang
is, after all, your future sister-in-law.
Are you going to hurt Qingyu
just for a woman?
You've made a mistake!
I made a mistake?
You're saying I made a mistake?
Why don't you say
Qingyu made a mistake?
Or that Fang Mulan made a mistake?
Qingyu and Miss Fang's relationship
is stable.
You know what kind of person
Qingyu is.
He will definitely protect Miss Fang
all his life.
They are a perfect match.
Why do you have to,
for the secret delusion in your heart,
turn the whole family upside down?
Delusion?
Do you know what a delusion is?
Let me tell you, Li Boze.
Your feelings for Hai Tangqing—
do you think others can't see them?
Ask yourself,
do you really know Hai Tangqing?
How do you know
she won't disappoint you?
Let me tell you, Li Boze.
Figure yourself out first
before judging me.
You're right.
Qingyi.
Let me tell you this too—
I may not know her,
but that doesn't stop me
from admiring her.
Do you understand?
Qingyi,
I'm different from you.
If she's interested in me,
I will pursue her seriously.
If she isn't,
I won't force her,
make things difficult for her,
or hurt her!
I will wait for her.
Qingyi.
To be honest,
I don't understand either.
But sometimes,
I think of Mother.
Look at her.
She loved Father deeply.
A finger bone,
or even a little bit of ashes,
she carries with her,
missing him madly.
And what about you and me?
The people we love
can live well in this world.
It doesn't matter
if we are together or not.
I feel like we're much luckier than Mother
being able to see them safe and happy.
Madam,
the lucky bags are ready.
Before the bride leaves,
we must ask her brothers
to use these golden scissors
to cut a lock of the bride's hair,
and place it in this bag
with Eldest Young Master Murong's hair,
tied together with a red string.
It signifies
a long-lasting union
and growing old together.
Once outside where there is light,
the bride's feet cannot touch the ground.
There...
The bride has no maiden family,
let alone a brother.
My father's passing
is known to Mother.
Who arranged this ceremony?
You didn't mention it earlier,
but had to wait
until all the guests arrived
and are already waiting downstairs
to bring it up.
This is bullying.
Calm down, miss.
I didn't know the bride's maiden family
was not around anymore.
They're holding this wedding right
after Master Fang's death.
I'm afraid they won't find anyone
in all of Nancheng
to carry her out.
Exactly.
Not observing filial piety,
she's so rotten.
Who says she doesn't have anyone?
Second Young Master?
He is the groom's brother.
How can he send the bride off?
Murong Qingyi?
Why are you here?
Young Master, you shouldn't...
There's no need to be so particular.
If tying a red string
could really
make people grow old together,
some people
wouldn't turn pale
at the mention of Yin Jingwan.
Compared to the Murong family,
I'm closer to you—
I'm more like your maiden family.
How about this—
when the bride is supposed to leave,
I'll carry you out.
♪ The more passionate ♪
I've figured it out.
♪ Our past embrace ♪
No matter who you marry,
it doesn't matter to me.
♪ The more icy ♪
Even if you are with my eldest brother,
♪ Our present clash ♪
I guess that will keep you
by my side forever.
Thinking about it this way,
♪ If not tangled in love ♪
the universally despised Murong family
♪ We are locked in hate ♪
has become much more interesting.
By the way,
♪ There is no escaping it ♪
As for the lucky bag,
I replaced the hair with mine.
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
The bride sets off!
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
♪ Love and hate till the very end ♪
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
[Murong Residence]
♪ Never back down, hold my ground ♪
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
♪ We ♪
♪ Must be together ♪
♪ Forevermore ♪
Stop pulling.
If you keep pulling,
the clothes will be ruined.
This is for you.
♪ How much love ♪
Inspector Li,
you should keep it for yourself.
♪ Is enough to be wasted? ♪
♪ I haven't forgiven you ♪
What's wrong lately?
♪ So don't you forgive me ♪
You've been avoiding me.
♪ Let the wildfire ♪
When you see me,
♪ Consume us and burn us to ashes ♪
it's like you've seen an enemy.
An enemy?
♪ Still, we choose to be moths ♪
That's an interesting choice of word,
Inspector Li.
♪ Flying into the flames ♪
Didn't we agree this is...
Agree on what?
♪ Must it take heartache ♪
♪ To know my heart belongs to you? ♪
Have I ever promised you anything,
Inspector Li?
♪ Hearts cold no more ♪
♪ Is every sweet dream ♪
♪ Destined to fade away? ♪
♪ Don't let it end in smoke ♪
What exactly is wrong?
♪ Love and hate till the very end ♪
Did something happen?
♪ Hold nothing back ♪
I am used to just putting on an act.
If there was any misunderstanding before,
♪ Never back down, hold my ground ♪
please pay no mind to it.
♪ Till I've given my all ♪
Our statuses are worlds apart.
♪ We ♪
After today,
♪ Must be together ♪
we shouldn't meet again.
♪ Forevermore ♪
I wish Inspector Li
a bright future.
If I didn't do something well enough
for you to like me,
♪ Take away everything I have ♪
♪ Can you bear the weight of it all? ♪
then I respect your choice.
♪ I offer you my whole life ♪
But you can't deprive me of
my right to like you.
♪ In exchange for my everything ♪
As long as there is no one else you fancy,
♪ Will you finally be mine? ♪
I will always like you
♪ Give me love and hate ♪
and wait for you.
♪ Let the tears fall ♪
♪ Let the blood spill ♪
♪ Even through suffering,
I'll never let go of your hand ♪
♪ I can't break free, I can't escape ♪
♪ This, too, can be called
a lifetime together ♪
It won't take long
♪ We ♪
♪ Remain bound by fate until the end ♪
for your feelings for me
♪ Forevermore ♪
to vanish into thin air.
♪ Neither you nor I ♪
The wedding car is here.
Let's go have a look.
The bride and groom
are entering the venue.
♪ Can ever break free ♪
Let's go.
You can leave first.
I'll handle the rest myself.
How is it?
Are you ready?
When the ceremony begins
and everyone is seated,
I'll be on the second floor,
waiting for the right moment
to assassinate Li Rongzhang.
Whether I succeed or not,
you must distance yourself from me
and pretend to know nothing about it.
During the ceremony,
I will go on stage first.
Come out.
Zhihong?
Qingyu.
I know about your plan.
I'm willing to help you.
You're saying you would marry in my place?
I know
that at the wedding,
you have something very important to do.
I can help cover for you.
This matter is very dangerous.
Don't get involved.
The wedding is the key to your success.
As long as there is a bride wearing a veil
to complete the ceremony with him,
no matter if
your operation succeeds or not,
he will have an excuse
to insist he knew nothing.
Then if I'm exposed,
you will naturally be exposed too.
What will you do then?
In that case,
it'd be my one-sided crush on Principal
that made me lose my mind,
leading me to deceive him
and become the substitute bride.
No matter what,
he must not be involved.
Let this fake wedding
have a pair of true lovers.
No matter what happens later,
don't take off the veil.
The bride
must be Miss Fang.
Rest assured.
I know.
Go prepare first.
It's not too late for you to back out now.
I won't back out.
Sorry.
You're doing this
to help me too after all,
right?
You should go prepare too.
Qingyi,
this time,
don't wait for me.